playgirl.com 2009-06-27

# PLAYGIRL - Privacy Policy

> **Privacy Policy**
> 
> **Trans Digital Media Privacy Policy**  
>  TRANS DIGITAL MEDIA has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering, use and dissemination practices for this Web site (the "Web site"). By using or accessing this Web site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE WEB SITE. 
> 
> **Personal and Non-Personal Information**  
>  When using the Web site you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself ("Personal Information"). Personal Information can include your name, email address, physical address or telephone number. In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other data, and may aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual ("Aggregate Information"). 
> 
> **Information Usage**  
>  We do not share any Personal Information you submit through our Web site with any third party, unless it is necessary to comply with your request for a service or product, or to comply with applicable law. We may use Aggregate Information to improve and enhance your experience on the Web site and for our market research activities. For example, we may share Aggregate Information with other unaffiliated third parties, such as business partners and advertisers, in an aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the shared information will not contain nor be linked to any Personal Information. We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party without your consent except in connection with the sale or merger of TRANS DIGITAL MEDIA or the division responsible for such services. 
> 
> **Changes to policy; Opt-Out Process**  
>  We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use Personal Information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of our Web site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. 
> 
> **Cookies**  
>  "Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. We, and the advertisers that place advertisements on the Web site, may use cookies to customize your visit to the Web site and for other purposes to make your visit more convenient or to enable us to enhance our service. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Web site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the Web site or your interaction with the Web site. 
> 
> **Clickstream**  
>  As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," can be collected and stored by a web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to the Web site. We may use clickstream data as a form of Aggregate Information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Web site, how visitors navigate throughout the Web site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information may be used to improve our Web site or to share with business partners or advertisers. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not contain any Personal Information. 
> 
> **Other Web Sites**  
>  Our Web site may contain links to, and advertisements from, other web sites not maintained by TRANS DIGITAL MEDIA. Other sites may also reference or link to our Web site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that you visit. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. 
> 
> **Security**   
>  The security of your Personal Information is very important to us. We attempt to provide for the secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers by utilizing encryption software. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and TRANS DIGITAL MEDIA., and TRANS DIGITAL MEDIA. and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the Web site demonstrates your assumption of this risk. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed access to your Personal Information. 
> 
> **Contact**  
>  For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: 
>
